DIPEN PRAJAPATI

CREDIT ANALYST

Credit analyst with more than 3 years of experience evaluating risk, identifying opportunities, and recommending solutions that support company goals Key achievement by reaching TAT of 75 % and more and Co ordination with Credit manager and Underwriters.

SKILLS

- Loan Servicing (Advanced))
- Negotiation (Experienced) Underwriting
- Risk Management
- Research

EDUCATION

GRADUATE

Bachelor of commerce

Gujarat University | 2016 - 2019

EXPERIENCE

FI AGENCY BACK OFFICE EXECUTIVE

KP associates 2019 - 2020 (6 months)

Learnt about Bank loan system process and Making Reports for loan verification. I have worked for products like IDFC home loan and IIFL home loan.

FI AGENCY BACK OFFICE EXECUTIVE

Sarvottam consultant 2020 - 2023

I have Worked here for IDFC Personal loan, Used car, New car, CD, Bil pl and credit card, etc products for more than 3 years. I have learnt about IDFC portal system and process for verification.

CONTACT

Email - dipenprajapati4040@gmail.com

Mobile - 9574270168